<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home</title>
    <link>https://blog.burrows.family/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Home</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 04 Jan 2021 08:49:37 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://blog.burrows.family/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Goodbye 2020</title>
      <link>https://blog.burrows.family/posts/goodbye-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jan 2021 08:49:37 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.burrows.family/posts/goodbye-2020/</guid>
      <description>As we look back, 2020 will be remembered but maybe not in the way that many of us thought. 2020 is behind us now, so it&amp;rsquo;s time to look forward to seeing what 2021 will bring us. Happy New Year!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Astroprint</title>
      <link>https://blog.burrows.family/posts/astroprint/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Oct 2020 18:20:08 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.burrows.family/posts/astroprint/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve been messing around with my new Creality CR-6 SE 3D printer recently. It&amp;rsquo;s a fantastic printer if you can overlook it&amp;rsquo;s newness flaws. 3D prints are typically created with a CAD application and saved to a .stl file. The .stl file then needs to be converted to gcode or &amp;ldquo;sliced&amp;rdquo; using a slicer application. Cura by Ultimaker is good slicer, but it does not currently have a printer profile for the Creality CR-6 SE 3D printer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Google Dynamic DNS</title>
      <link>https://blog.burrows.family/posts/google-dynamic-dns/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Oct 2020 19:24:55 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.burrows.family/posts/google-dynamic-dns/</guid>
      <description>Running a hobby server at home can be a great way to learn something new. Hobby Linux servers have been a passion of mine for their simplicity and cost. They can be a quick way to kick the tires on an interesting CRM, ticket system, media server, etc. One of my favorite sites for this is TurnKey Linux.   While testing on a local hobby server may work just fine for most situations, there may be an instance where you want to have a public or remote access to your server.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Have I Been Pwned</title>
      <link>https://blog.burrows.family/posts/have-i-been-pwned/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Oct 2020 08:45:45 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.burrows.family/posts/have-i-been-pwned/</guid>
      <description>Here&amp;rsquo;s a fun little project that lets you check offline if your password has been pwned. Download the SHA-1 password database here and name it pwned-passwords-sha1-ordered-by-count-v6.txt. Then copy the following text into a BeenPwned.sh file in the same directory as the password hash that was downloaded. When run it will prompt for &amp;ldquo;Password to search:&amp;rdquo;. Type in a password and press enter. The script will hash the password you typed and check the hash agains the database.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://blog.burrows.family/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Oct 2020 08:45:20 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.burrows.family/about/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m always trying something new. Currently you are looking at my attempt to learn Hugo.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://blog.burrows.family/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Oct 2020 08:26:26 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.burrows.family/contact/</guid>
      <description>This is just a placeholder for a page in this theme.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Pastebin Features</title>
      <link>https://blog.burrows.family/posts/new-pastebin-features/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Oct 2020 08:46:07 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.burrows.family/posts/new-pastebin-features/</guid>
      <description>I stumbled across this today while looking for a snippet of code on my Pastebin account.
There are two new features that can be used when creating a new Paste.
   An individual password can be assigned to each Paste. There an option for &amp;ldquo;Burn after read&amp;rdquo; that can be enabled for each new Paste.  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hugo Shortcode</title>
      <link>https://blog.burrows.family/posts/hugo-shortcode/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Oct 2020 08:40:05 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.burrows.family/posts/hugo-shortcode/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m trying to setup and use Hugo to make a personal blog for collecting thoughts and documenting test results from tinkering.
I&amp;rsquo;m using the Coder Theme theme for Hugo. I&amp;rsquo;ve made enough changes to it that it can no longer be updated from Git. Little tweaks like changing the Google Fonts, fixing mismatch header sizes, modifications to layouts, etc. I&amp;rsquo;ve managed to get CloudApp working as a Shortcode.
Here&amp;rsquo;s an video from CloudApp about the Have I Been Pwned local script.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>